hostgeni.net 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy

The privacy of your personal information is afforded the highest level of importance by HostGeni. We are bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Act”) regarding the manner in which we handle your personal information and how we respond to your requests to access and correct it. While we take careful measurements to protect the confidentiality of information provided to us, we have adopted the Privacy Policy detailed in this document in compliance with the Act. This document sets out our information handling procedures and the rights and obligations that both you and we have in relation to your personal information. Collection of Information We will only collect personal information where it is reasonably necessary to do so for the conduct of our business. Any collection of personal information by us will be fair and lawful and will not be intrusive. Upon request you will be told the identity of the collecting entity, the purpose of the collection, details on how you can gain access to your personal information and any consequences of failing to give the information. If it is reasonable and practical do so, we will collect personal information about you only from you. In the course of operating the business, however, it may be necessary to collect personal information from various external sources, including government agencies and other third parties. If we collect personal information about you from a third party we will, where appropriate, request that the third party inform you that we are holding such information, how we will use and disclose it, and that you may contact us to gain access to and correct and update the information. We will not, however, make any such request to any third party in circumstances where it would not be practical to do so. Use and Disclosure of Information In general, we will not use or disclose personal information about you otherwise than for the purpose of providing or offering goods and services to you, for any other purpose that you may reasonably expect, for any other purpose authorised by law, or for any other purposes disclosed to or authorised by you. This may include disclosures to organisations that provide us with professional advice, such as solicitors, accountants and business advisors. A number of laws require the provision of personal information to third parties. The precise information required to be provided will vary depending on the circumstances requiring disclosure of that information. We will, wherever possible, keep all personal information strictly confidential. Any disclosure that is required to be made to any third party will be made primarily for the purpose of providing or offering goods and services to you. Any personal information submitted via our online form may need to be processed by a third party. By submitting personal information via an online form, you consent to the disclosure of that information to a third party, which may be located overseas, for the sole purpose of processing the online form. We may also use or disclose personal information about you to avoid, lessen or prevent a serious emergency or crime. If we use or disclose personal information about you in those circumstances we will make a written record of such use or disclosure. Information Security We will take reasonable steps to hold all hard copy and electronic records of your information in a secure manner to ensure that they are protected from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. We will delete your personal information once it is no longer needed or required to be kept by law. Data Access and Correction You may request access to your personal information at any time by sending a written request to our privacy officer by email. You do not need to provide a reason for your request. We may charge a small fee for providing access if it requires a significant amount of time to locate or collect your information or to present it in an appropriate form. In rare circumstances, and only where it is permitted under the Act, we may not be able to provide you with access to your information. For example, where the requested access will have an unreasonable impact upon the privacy of others or where we are required by law to withhold the information, we may refuse access. If we are unable to provide you with access, we will provide you with reasons for our refusal. If your personal information is out of date or incorrect, you may inform us of this and we will correct it for you. Transfer of Information Overseas By submitting personal information to HostGeni, you consent to the transfer of that information to any jurisdiction in which HostGeni conducts its business activities, for the purpose of enabling HostGeni to provide services to you. We will otherwise only transfer your personal information overseas if the transfer is to you or to one of your authorised representatives, with your expressed consent or otherwise in accordance with the National Privacy Principles. 

**Read on phone/iPad**
